[theme music playing]
[Ivy] Thirteen years. I longed for you.
And now, Mom? I'm with you again.
But it hurts because
you can't remember me.
[Diego] I'll do everything
to find out the truth.
I just want answers to my questions.
So I can freely love Ivy… or Lily.
[Arnaldo] Carlotta, I know Ivy's
hiding something from me.
And I swear, I'll find out what it is.
Be honest with me. What's
going on between you and Ivy?
-Nothing.
-She's missing!
Did you kidnap her
so you could get back at Grandpa?
Your grandfather is just using that woman.
Right now, she's useful to him.
But he'll eventually get rid of her too.
Just like you and your mom!
[Julio] My daughter, Emilia.
She has been diagnosed
with ovarian cancer, stage 2.
I need to step down as
the governor of this province.
[Julio] Governor Emilia's successor
will be Governor William Alvarez!
[teacher] Ivy?
According to Mrs. Aguas,
Ivy went through a lot.
Something to do with
her childhood and her real mom.
-[Diego] Hold on. Her real mom?
-[teacher] Yes.
Ivy is Mrs. Aguas' adopted daughter.
[Diego] You don't have to lie anymore.
I already know who Ivy really is.
[Julio] I want you to take
all of Emilia's and Raul's belongings,
and move them to the old guesthouse
at the back of our house.
I promise I'll return
to that mansion! I swear it!
[sobbing] Lily. Lily!
[Ivy] Yes. That's me. I'm Lily.
Do you remember me now?
Do you remember me now, Mom?
It's me. I'm Lily.
[sobbing]
You're not Lily.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Lily's my daughter. I have to save her.
Lily's in danger. You have to help me.
-But, Mom…
-Help me. Let's look for Lily.
I have to get out of here.
I need to find Lily.
-But, Mom…
-I'm begging you. Help me.
[sobbing] Help me find Lily.
I need to get out of here.
[sobbing uncontrollably]
Okay.
I'll help you.
I'll help you… I'll help you find Lily.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
[instrumental theme music playing]
[Camia sniffles]
Lily.
[breathing heavily]
[Camia] Lily.
Lily, my baby, wherever you are…
please know I love you so much.
[sniffles]
I love you so much.
You know what?
Wherever Lily might be right now…
I'm sure she misses you a lot.
I'm sure Lily loves you so much.
And she wants to be with you.
That's why I'll help you find Lily.
But if you really want to see Lily again…
then we need to get out of here.
We need to leave this house
if you still want to see Lily.
Yes. Yes, let's leave.
I want to hug my daughter again.
["Wildflower" by Arnel Pineda playing]
♪ Let her cry, for she's a lady… ♪
[Camia] Lily…
♪ Let her dream ♪
♪ For she's a child ♪
♪ She's a child ♪
♪ Let the rain fall down upon her ♪
♪ She's a free and gentle flower
Growing wild ♪
I won't rest easy
until I get to talk to Ivy.
I want to hear the truth
straight from her.
But Ivy's missing.
What if she's hiding from you?
Or maybe she found out that
you already know her secret.
Diego, Miss Aguas is a good person.
But considering the fact
that she kept all these things from you,
I have a feeling she's up to
something against your family.
[Pandoy] What will you do now, Diego?
Will you warn your family
against Miss Aguas?
-[tense music playing]
-[sighs]
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-Sir Diego.
Your grandfather is asking for you.
[foreboding music playing]
[screaming]
Help!
[cries] Nanny, help! Ouch!
My eyes! Ouch! Nanny!
Arnaldo! The water's been cut off!
Oh, it hurts! Nanny! Arnaldo!
Ouch! It hurts!
[crying]
Ouch.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I can't see! I can't see! Ow!
-[Arnaldo] Mom?
-Arnaldo!
Hey, what happened here? What's wrong?
[crying]
The water's been cut off!
-Arnaldo!
-Why did this happen?
It's been a long time
since this house was lived in.
The pipes are broken.
-[crying]
-[phone ringing]
[Emilia] Your grandfather
is maltreating me.
-I hate him!
-[ringing continues]
Can you please turn that off?!
It's so noisy!
I'm sorry, Governor. My mother's calling.
I don't care if your mother's calling!
[crying]
Arnaldo!
[crying] No water. My eyes hurt.
And you, Raul, why aren't you helping?!
If you think Papa will only punish me,
then you're wrong!
He wants us both to rot in hell!
My life here is so miserable.
Look at the house. It's so old!
-Arnaldo, do something.
-Yes. Yes.
I'll do something about it.
[Emilia] Thank you.
[phone ringing]
Nanny, didn't I tell you not to call me?
I'm sorry, Jepoy. But it's an emergency.
Diego found out that Ivy is Lily.
[suspenseful music playing]
What if he tells the Ardientes?
But, how…
Nanny, Diego's here.
Stop him!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[breathes heavily]
Have a drink.
Thank you.
[soft music playing]
Thank you for helping me.
Don't worry. We'll get out of here.
You know what?
You look beautiful when you smile.
You look like my daughter, Lily.
You're very beautiful too.
Uh…
Can I call you "Mom"?
I just really miss my mom.
Okay.
Thank you, Mom.
[foreboding music playing]
Grandpa.
Oh. Diego, my grandson. Come, sit down.
Grandpa, what do you want from me?
Um…
Actually, it's not you whom I need.
It's…
Miss Ivy Aguas.
I have some unfinished business
with that woman.
But unfortunately,
she just vanished into thin air.
And as far as I know,
when a person is in hiding…
it means they're concealing some secrets.
[tense music playing]
You must be tired. Come, let's eat.
[knife clinks]
-Here.
-Thank you, Mom.
You know…
You remind me of my husband, Dante.
He was very hardworking.
Even if he was tired,
he'd help me with the chores.
Lily really took after him.
Hold on.
Lily had a best friend.
Diego.
Could Lily be with him?
You remember Diego?
You're always with Miss Aguas, right?
Um…
Oh.
You helped the farmers together.
And I heard that you've become
quite attached to this woman.
[dark dramatic music playing]
What?
Where did you hear that?
[chuckling]
Oh, Diego.
There's not a thing in my town
that I don't know about.
[Camia] Yes.
He was my daughter's best friend.
He'll help us. Let's ask him for help.
I'm sure he'll help us get out of here.
That's too risky.
We're not sure if…
if we can trust him.
Why do you say that?
I'm sure… Diego would help Lily.
[Julio] Why?
Will you go against your own family
for that woman?
Don't, Diego.
Because that will make you a traitor.
Now, where is Miss Aguas, and…
what do you know about her?
What?!
Answer me!
I'll ask again.
Where is Miss Aguas?
Where is she hiding?
Ivy is a good person, Grandpa.
She helped the farmers
get what the politicians
long promised them.
And even if I knew where Ivy was…
I wouldn't tell you.
[scoffs]
You idiot!
[suspenseful music playing]
Go ahead, Grandpa. Try me.
I'm not the same kid you used to abuse.
You can't scare me.
[Julio sets down crutch]
Who do you think you are?
I raised you!
I fed you and sent you to school.
Don't ever think that you can
go against this family.
Even though you're my grandson,
I won't think twice about killing you!
[suspenseful music playing]
Grandpa, I'm not scared of you.
I'm just fighting for what's right.
I'm ashamed to even call you an Ardiente.
I don't want to see your face.
Get out of my sight! Leave!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
Mom, for now, we can't
be sure of anything.
Nowadays, we don't know
whom we should trust,
or whom we can trust.
You and me.
Right now, we only have each other.
Just you and me.
You're a brave woman.
But I can feel you're a good person too.
I'm sure your parents are so proud of you.
Thank you.
It's good to know that…
you hid Ivy's true identity
from your grandfather.
Uncle, I won't reveal Ivy's secret.
I know she has a reason
for doing what she's doing.
But you need to talk to her.
Fooling the Ardientes
like that is no joke.
With how cruel your family is,
her days are numbered
if they learn her secret.
I'll sort all this out. I'll look for Ivy.
How will you find her?
Where will you start?
Who knows where she is?
[suspenseful music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
Where are you going?
Where are you going?!
You're going to leave me?!
You bastard. You haven't changed at all!
What's this?! Are you leaving me?!
You're going to your mistress again?!
Huh?! Answer me!
[unzips bag]
This is mine. This is mine!
You gave this to me
as a gift last Valentine's Day!
Now you're giving it
to your mistress?! You bastard!
When will you stop cheating on me?!
Why? Are you so sick of me?
So you run off
with that loose woman of yours?!
Go on, do it. I'll burn her to ashes!
Give me that. All you do is talk.
-You're not leaving.
-Get out of the way!
No! I won't let you leave, Raul!
-I said--
-Don't try me!
-Step aside!
-Guards! Guards!
Deal with this man.
Now go ahead and try to leave.
And don't you ever try
giving this to your mistress!
This is mine!
You take care of him!
[suspenseful music playing]
[door slams]
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Nanny.
Yes.
I'm at the place where I last
saw Ivy before she went missing.
Maybe I'll find clues
that'll point me to her.
Yes, Nanny. Don't worry. I'll be careful.
[tense music playing]
What are you doing here?
[Emilia] It's so hot.
[foreboding music playing]
[Julio] Good morning, Emilia.
[Emilia] Good morning, Papa.
Stop. You don't have to act nice.
There aren't any cameras here.
I just came to know
how your first night here was.
I heard you and your husband
were fighting like cats
and dogs again last night.
That was nothing, Papa.
It's normal for couples
to have petty lovers' quarrels.
[chuckles]
"Petty lovers' quarrel."
The quarrel was petty, but…
the reason behind it was not.
I'm warning you, Emilia,
you're pulling each other down.
And I won't let you drag
my name down with you.
You're a failure as a wife.
A failure as a mother.
You're a failure as a governor.
Most of all,
you're a failure as a daughter.
[gloomy music playing]
I am not a failure, Papa.
I am not a failure.
I… I'm going to a farm.
What are you doing here?
This is where I last saw Ivy Aguas.
Grandpa asked me to find her.
Are you looking for her too?
What? Why would I look for Ivy?
I don't need anything from her.
[exhales sharply]
Be careful.
If I find out you're betraying us again…
I'll forget you're my brother.
[tense music playing]
-That's enough.
-No, Mom.
We need to get out of here…
before that bastard Raul comes back again.
-That's enough. That's enough.
-No, Mom.
-We need to get out of here!
-That's enough.
That's enough.
[soft piano music playing]
Mom, I'm sorry if I woke you up.
[mysterious music playing]
Hello? Anyone here?
Yes?
-Uh… Good afternoon.
-Good afternoon to you too.
The owner of that car…
where is she?
Mister, I'm her friend.
Her name's Ivy Aguas.
She's been missing for a few days now,
so please tell me where she is.
Uh… She went to the old Torillo house
here in San Ildefonso.
Raul Torillo?
Yes.
Why did she go there?
I don't know.
I've not seen her again
since she left her car here.
Thank you.
[instrumental theme music playing]
You know…
I'm a teacher.
You can't force things to happen.
You need patience.
You need to think things through
before you act.
[instrumental theme music playing]
[line ringing]
[loudly] Nanny, Uncle.
I'm heading to San Ildefonso.
I heard…
that Ivy went to Dad's old house there.
What's Miss Aguas doing there?
What is she doing with your dad?
I don't know.
They both left Arnaldo's party
at the same time.
But I'm not sure.
Could've been a coincidence.
Could Raul know about Miss Aguas' secret?
That's what I need to find out.
Do you know how to get there?
No, Uncle. Dad never took us there before.
But…
I'll just ask around for directions.
Take care, Diego.
Don't worry about me.
[tense music playing]
[dark piano music playing]
[Jepoy] Hi, Governor.
I'm sorry, I thought no one was here.
Madrigal? They call you "Madrigal," right?
Yes, Governor.
Come join me for a drink.
I'm sorry, Governor.
We aren't allowed to drink
during working hours.
Says who?
My boss.
Well, who are you guarding right now?
Me, right?
So, that means I'm your boss.
Sit and join me for a drink.
[ice clinks in glass]
-Grandpa.
-Oh.
Arnaldo, sit down. Join me for some tea.
It looks like you're home early.
Uh, Grandpa, I wasn't able
to get any news on Miss Aguas.
I went to the last place
where I saw her,
but I still didn't get anything.
And you just gave up?
You know, Arnaldo, I don't remember…
teaching you to be weak.
No, Grandpa. I'm not giving up.
I came home early to check
on Mama at the guesthouse.
Exactly what I'm talking about.
Your mother is pulling you down.
[dark dramatic music playing]
A hunter who shows his weaknesses…
soon becomes the hunted.
So, don't be weak like your parents.
Madrigal, how long have you
been working for us?
Five or six years?
That sounds about right, Governor.
So that means, you know me.
And you know my husband very well.
So, do you think my husband
is having an affair?
I'm sorry, Governor.
I have no right to interfere
with your married life.
[dark piano music playing]
Do you think I'm capable
of cheating on my husband?
[sighs]
How I wish I could.
But even if I do it in front of him…
the question is, would he even care?
Or would I end up getting hurt?
You see, Madrigal, my husband's
had so many mistresses.
But not one of them succeeded
in taking him from me.
So, I'm thinking that this woman…
is just one of those cheap mistresses…
that I can easily wipe off
the face of the earth.
[suspenseful music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
Mom?
[lock clicks]
[birds chirping]
Mom?
[knocking]
Are you okay?
Mom, what's wrong?
Nothing. I just used the restroom.
Uh… Come on. Get some rest.
Sit there, Mom. I need to keep
-tearing down the wall.
-[car engine starts]
That sounds like a car.
Diego?
-Diego!
-[pounding on window]
Diego!
Diego, we're here! Diego!
He already left.
Mom, that was Diego. My childhood--
Lily's childhood friend.
Diego.
Diego?
Yes.
He's Lily's childhood friend.
Don't worry. They'll find a way
to get us out of this house.
But how will they find us
in a place like this?
I don't know.
But I believe that they will
be able to find us.
I'll save you. I'll find a way.
I'll save you.
[tense music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
Sir, this is all we got from the kitchen.
Oh. Are you sure?
You hid some of it, didn't you?
[chuckles]
Go ahead. Let's drink.
What if the congressman sees us?
Oh, come on! You're already
holding your glasses.
We used to do this before. Right?
Look. Can you say no to this?
It's your favorite.
Right? Besides, we're the only ones here.
No one will get mad at us. Come on.
-[glasses clink]
-Bottoms up!
I went to my dad's house,
but Ivy Aguas wasn't there.
That house is empty most of the time, sir.
I only saw Mr. Torillo
once or twice there.
Maybe, this Ivy you're looking
for isn't here in San Ildefonso.
Chief, her car was found here.
She couldn't just disappear
all of a sudden.
What if something bad happened to her?
What should we do?
Who is this Ivy Aguas anyway?
And why is she here in San Ildefonso?
Maybe, she… You know what I mean.
[both laugh]
Or maybe, she's Raul Torillo's mistress.
It's the talk of the town…
that your dad is a womanizer.
[cop Manansala] But don't worry.
We'll go to that house.
We'll also tell our other officers
to help you find Ivy Aguas.
Thank you.
Let's have another drink. Hey!
Hey!
Psst!
Let's have another round.
Hey. Gave up already?
[sinister music playing]
[car alarm chirps]
[car engine starts]
[Emilia] I'll find out who
your mistress is, Raul.
Then, you'll see.
Come with me.
[vehicle approaching]
Someone's coming.
Mom, it's Raul. Raul's back.
[suspenseful music playing]
Mom, listen to me.
Raul can't know I'm here.
He can't know you aren't alone.
If he does, I'm sure he'll hurt you.
He'll hurt us both.
[car alarm chirps]
Don't worry, Mom.
I promise I'll find a way
to get us out of here…
so we can find Lily, right?
We'll find Lily.
Love?
[foreboding music playing]
Mom, I'll be hiding now.
-[Raul] Jasmin?
-[Ivy] Don't tell him I'm here.
Jasmin, I'm home.
Love?
Love.
[tense music playing]
How are you?
Did you eat well here? Huh?
I'm sorry I couldn't come back sooner.
I just had to settle everything
I had to settle,
so we can live happily together,
without any problems,
and with no one
bothering us anymore. Okay?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Raul] You're going to love
what I brought you.
These are for you.
This one, it's pretty.
This will look really good on you.
Some toiletries. We need these.
Clothes. Here. I brought a lot.
Let's see if it fits you.
This looks…
[laughing]
So-- Sorry.
I didn't know…
I think they're too big for you.
Anyway, don't worry.
Next time I go to the store,
I'll buy the right sizes, okay? I promise.
I'll just return these clothes.
But first, I'll sort our stuff out.
I'll put these in your closet.
[Raul] We don't want our stuff
scattered here, you know?
What's wrong?
What is it, love?
I'm hungry.
[bag thuds]
Did you just say you're hungry?
You can talk now?
Thank goodness.
Love, you don't know how happy
you made me today.
I guess I should buy us some food first.
Then, we'll celebrate, okay?
I love you so much. I won't be long.
Raul…
Come back, okay?
I promise. I'll be back.
[suspenseful music playing]
Mom.
We have to leave
before that bastard comes back.
But how?
[suspenseful music playing]
Santos. Do it now.
You chose the wrong man to flirt with.
[suspenseful dramatic music playing]
It's done, Governor.
You can go now, Santos.
Leave the keys with me.
Here.
Fifty thousand.
-Like what we agreed on.
-Thank you. Thank you, ma'am.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia humming]
[laughing]
One great move, Emilia.
Good job.
[suspenseful music playing]
[fire crackling]
[laughing maniacally]
[Camia] Fire! Fire!
[laughing]
-[Camia] Fire!
-[Ivy] Mom.
[Camia] Fire!
Fire!
[breathing heavily]
[Camia coughing]
[Ivy] Mom!
Mom, put this on.
[coughing]
[fire whooshing]
[laughing]
[coughing]
[Ivy] Wait here.
[water running]
Here, Mom.
[both coughing]
Hold on, Mom.
[Camia screams] We're going to die here!
[Ivy] No, we're not!
[Camia] We're going to die!
No, Mom! I'll get us out of here!
[both coughing]
[fire whooshing]
-[laughing maniacally]
-[pounding on wall continues]
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[fire whooshing]
[wood clatters]
[coughing]
[Ivy] Careful, Mom.
Poor girl.
[Ivy] Wait here, Mom.
[Emilia] Your poor mistress, Raul.
Nothing will be left of her.
Toasted to death.
[chuckles]
Even her soul will burn.
[coughing]
[Ivy] Come here, Mom!
-[thudding, clattering]
-[screaming]
-Mom!
-[fire whooshing]
[laughing]
Mom!
Mom, come here! Mom!
[suspenseful music playing]
Hello, Raul? Come back here.
I have a surprise for you.
What are you talking about, Emilia?
Where will I go back?
Where else? To the house of your mistress.
Jepoy, do you have any news on Ivy?
My gut's telling me
-that if I find Raul,
-Mom!
[Jepoy] I'll find Ivy too.
-[Ivy] Wait!
-[Camia coughing]
[Raul sobbing] Jasmin!
-I'm here.
-[laughing]
This isn't over, Emilia!
[Emilia] The easiest way
to get rid of your enemies
is to kill them.
Because once you do that,
that means you've won.
[theme music playing]